[
  {
    "question": "What is the most cost-effective option to have 24x7 phone, email, and chat support?",
    "options": [
      "Basic Support Plan",
      "Developer Support Plan",
      "Enterprise Support Plan",
      "Business Support Plan"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "What can you use to estimate the cost of your architecture solution?",
    "options": [
      "Pricing Calculator",
      "Cost and Usage Reports",
      "Total Cost of Ownership (TCO)",
      "Trusted Advisor"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "The Enterprise Support Plan comes with a business-critical system down response under 15 minutes and offers access to a Technical Account Manager",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "A company is not sure whether or not it is cost-effective to migrate to the AWS Cloud. Which service can help the executive board make a decision?",
    "options": [
      "Billing Dashboard",
      "Support Plans",
      "Pricing Calculator",
      "AWS Documentation"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "What can you use to get alerts when your costs and usage are exceeding or are forecasted to exceed your budgeting amount?",
    "options": [
      "Cost and Usage Reports",
      "Billing Dashboard",
      "Pricing Calculator",
      "Budgets"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "When you reserve, the larger the upfront payment, the smaller the discount.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False, the upfront payment does not matter on the discount",
      "False, the larger the upfront, the bigger the discount"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are design principles of Performance Efficiency?",
    "options": [
      "Go global in minutes & Use serverless architectures",
      "Adopt a consumption mode & Stop spending money on data center operations",
      "Understand your impact & Maximize utilization",
      "Perform operations as code"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "Testing recovery procedures, and automatically recover from failure are design principles of Performance Efficiency.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Automate security best practices, apply security at all layers, and protect data in transit and at rest are design principles of:",
    "options": [
      "Operational Excellence",
      "Security",
      "Reliability",
      "Performance Efficiency"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "AWS Trusted Advisor comes with Full checks in the Developer Support Plan",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "For certain services like Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) and Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS), you can invest in reserved capacity. What options are available for Reserved Instances? (Choose three.)",
    "options": [
      "AURI (All Upfront Reserved Instances)",
      "MURI",
      "NURI (No Upfront Reserved Instances)",
      "PURI (Partial Upfront Reserved Instances)",
      "DURI"
    ],
    "correctIndex": [
      0,
      2,
      3
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where can a customer go to get more details about Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) billing activity that took place 3 months ago?",
    "options": [
      "Amazon EC2 dashboard",
      "AWS Cost Explorer",
      "AWS Trusted Advisor dashboard",
      "AWS CloudTrail logs stored in Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3)"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? To receive the discounted rate associated with Reserved Instances, you must make a full, upfront payment for the term of the agreement.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Which statement is true about the pricing model on AWS?",
    "options": [
      "In most cases, there is a per gigabyte charge for inbound data transfer.",
      "Storage is typically charged per gigabyte.",
      "Compute is typically charged as a monthly fee based on instance type.",
      "Outbound charges are free up to a per account limit."
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the four support plans offered by AWS Support?",
    "options": [
      "Basic, Developer, Business, Enterprise",
      "Basic, Startup, Business, Enterprise",
      "Free, Bronze, Silver, Gold",
      "All support is free"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "What AWS tool lets you explore AWS services and create an estimate for the cost of your use cases on AWS?",
    "options": [
      "AWS Pricing Calculator",
      "AWS Budgets",
      "AWS Cost and Usage Report",
      "AWS Billing Dashboard"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "As AWS grows, the cost of doing business is reduced and savings are passed back to the customer with lower pricing. What is this optimization called?",
    "options": [
      "Expenditure awareness",
      "Economies of scale",
      "Matching supply and demand",
      "EC2 Right Sizing"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? AWS offers some services at no charge, such as, Amazon Virtual Private Cloud, AWS Identity and Access Management, Consolidated Billing, AWS Elastic Beanstalk, automatic scaling, AWS OpsWorks and AWS CloudFormation. However, you might be charged for other AWS services that you use in conjunction with these services.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "What are benefits of using AWS Organizations? (Choose two.)",
    "options": [
      "Replaces existing AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) policies with service control policies (SCPs)",
      "Provides the ability to create groups of accounts and then attach policies to a group",
      "Provides the ability to create an unlimited number of nested organizational units (OUs)",
      "Simplifies automating account creation and management by using APIs",
      "Prevents any restrictions from being put on the root user"
    ],
    "correctIndex": [
      1,
      3
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? Unlimited services are available with the AWS Free Tier to new AWS customers for 12 months following their AWS sign-up date.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  }
]